trackcourier.io 2019-05-01

# Privacy

At TrackCourier.io we take privacy of our visitors very seriously. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by TrackCourier.io and how we use it.

#### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, TrackCourier.io makes use of log files. These files merely log visitors to the site - usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

We use cookies to enhance and simplify your visit in order to offer easier surfing on the website, for internal security purposes, for system administration. Cookies are small data files stored on the hard disk of the users’ computer. In addition to cookies which send information to us, we also use cookies which collect information and send it to third parties. An example of this is Google Analytics. Some of our cookies may collect and store your personal information, such as your name or email address. By using this Website, you agree to the placement of cookies on your computer and to TrackCourier.io’s access to cookies in accordance with the terms herein. If you do not wish to accept cookies from the Website please either disable cookies or refrain from using the website.

We may also use web beacons. Web beacons allow us to understand if a certain page of the Website was visited or if an email was opened or if advertising banners on other websites were effective.

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually set your browser to remove or reject cookies, but note that doing so does not necessarily affect third party flash cookies used in conjunction with our Website. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of the Website and you may not be able to access or use some or all areas and functionalities of the Website.

#### Our Advertising Partner

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our only advertising partner currently is Google.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on TrackCourier.io and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site's third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

TrackCourier.io has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

#### Third Party Privacy Policies

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. TrackCourier.io's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites. You may find a comprehensive listing of these privacy policies and their links here: Privacy Policy Links.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. What Are Cookies?

#### Children's Information

We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity. TrackCourier.io does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that TrackCourier.io has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (using the contact in the first paragraph) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

#### Online Privacy Policy Only

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

#### Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

#### Update

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 12-JAN-2018

Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us through our feedback form.
